// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Find the noun ",
    que_img_url : "",
    answer: "room",
    options: [
      "once",
      "room",
      "how",
      "None of these"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Find the noun ",
    que_img_url : "",
    answer: "uncle",
    options: [
      "uncle",
      "from",
      "how",
      "None of these"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Find the pronoun ",
    que_img_url : "",
    answer: "his",
    options: [
      "why",
      "are",
      "his",
      "None of these"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Complete sentence with appropriate verb. \"The dog _ _ _\" ",
    que_img_url : "",
    answer: "runs",
    options: [
      "when",
      "are",
      "runs",
      "None of these"
    ]
  },

    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Complete sentence with appropriate verb. \"Ram _ _ _ a mango.\" ",
    que_img_url : "",
    answer: "eats",
    options: [
      "eats",
      "thanks",
      "pet",
      "great"
    ]
  },
  
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which is not adjective",
    que_img_url : "",
    answer: "run",
    options: [
      "great",
      "beautiful",
      "two",
      "run"
    ]
  }
  ,
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Find the adjective \"Tortoises are slow animals.\" ",
    que_img_url : "",
    answer: "slow",
    options: [
      "Tortoises",
      "are",
      "slow",
      "animals"
    ]
  }
  /*
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "A boy had total 50 pens. He gave equal pens among 10 friends, How many pens each friend get?",
    que_img_url : "",
    answer: "5",
    options: [
      "5",
      "6",
      "4",
      "3"
    ]
  },
  
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "There are total 20 soaps and packets comes with 4 soaps per packet. How many such packets will be there?",
    que_img_url : "",
    answer: "5",
    options: [
        "5",
        "6",
        "4",
        "3"
      ]
  },
  /*
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: " 9 * 9 = ?",
    que_img_url : "",
    answer: "81",
    options: [
      "18",
      "88",
      "17",
      "81"
    ]
  }
  */
];
